<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AudioVideoPlayer</string>
    <string name="open">OPEN</string>
    <string name="close">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="unlock_with_fingerprint">Enable Authentication</string>
    <string name="about">AudioVideoPlayer application is an application that runs on Android Operating System where the user can listen to songs and watch videos on the go. The application loads the audio and video files from the internal storage and the user can tap on video/audio according to his/her preference. The features of this application is described below:</string>
    <string-array name="features">
        <item>In this application user can watch videos or listen to the music/ audio of the video in the background even when the user leaves the application.</item>
        <item>When the application is launched for the first time User has to provide internal storage access to load files.</item>
        <item>User can watch the video in fullscreen or stretch the video to fullscreen.</item>
        <item>User can enable authentication to protect privacy.</item>
        <item>A Gif is added in the Audio UI to indicate the song which is currently getting played.</item>
        <item>User can control the playback of audio/video from notification or from the player activity.</item>
        <item>User has an option to change the layout of Video files list into single or double grid.</item>
        <item>User can set sleep timer to terminate the application after the user defined time is elapsed.</item>
        <item>User has Seekbar option in the notification if the application runs on Android Version Q(10) or higher.</item>
        <item>User has Search functionality to search for a particular song or video using the title.</item>
        <item>User has an option to share video or audio files using third party applications.</item>
        <item>If the user disconnects the bluetooth headsets/ buds during the media playback,the media playback will be paused.</item>
        <item>Moreover, as an additional feature if the user is listening to songs or watching videos in another application or if the user is attending to calls, then the media playback of this current application is paused and vice versa.</item>
        <item>If the user cancels the notification entire application gets terminated or can also be terminated using exit app option.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>